<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Featured | Luis Cacho</title>
    <link>/categories/featured/</link>
      <atom:link href="/categories/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Featured</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>es-mx</language><copyright>© 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 02:08:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/lc-profile.png</url>
      <title>Featured</title>
      <link>/categories/featured/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soy un Racker</title>
      <link>/post/im-a-racker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 02:08:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/im-a-racker/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desde el 6 de Enero estoy trabajando en &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rackspace&lt;/a&gt;, the Open Cloud Company, eso significa que soy un Racker desde hace 3 meses y estoy amando cada minuto que ha pasado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/im-a-racker/Rackspace_2014.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rackspace 2014&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;previo&#34;&gt;Previo&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todo comenzo en Noviembre de 2013, cuando un Reclutador Técnico me contacto y comenzamos un proceso largo y exhaustivo de entrevistas. pruebas de habilidades, papeleo, etc, Acepte comenzar a trabajar como Administrador Linux I en el equipo dedicado a LATAM en Rackspace, entonces, ¡Estoy trabajando en una de las compañias técnologicas mas dínamicas, fánaticas, y divertidas del mundo!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En resumidas cuentas, estaba super emocionado, nervioso, feliz, todo al mismo tiempo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;el-castillo&#34;&gt;El Castillo&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desde que llegue al Castillo, todo ha sido maravilloso, he conocido gente amable, inteligente y fánatica, como por ejemplo &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/rackersugarbear&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;@SugarBear&lt;/a&gt;, un embajador de la cultura de Rackspace, o &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/gweston&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Graham Weston&lt;/a&gt;, el director y co-fundador de Rackspace, los conocí en la Orientación de novatos (a.k.a Rookie&amp;rsquo;O), donde invertimos tiempo con otros novatos aprendiendo acerca de la historia de Rackspace, su cultura y los planes a futuro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En el Rookie&amp;rsquo;O, me sorprendí y admire toda la energía que se transmitía entre los nuevos Rackers, ¡fue asombroso!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los Valores de Rackspace me inspiraron:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soporte Fánatico en todo lo que hagamos (Fanatical Support® in all we do).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resultados primero, sustancia sobre rapidez (Results first, substance over flash).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprometido con la grandeza (Committed to Greatness).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Total transparencia (Full Disclosure and Transparency).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pasión por nuestro trabajo (Passion for our Work).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tratar a los Rackers como amigos y familiares (Treat fellow Rackers like Friends and Family).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which from my point of view I can applied to my personal life, and having great results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also is very comfortable to have a Coffe Shop, a soda machine or microwaves inside the Castle. It is pretty nice!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general the first week in Rackspace, on the Rookie&amp;rsquo;O, I was a great experience, I can say that is one of my best experiences in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/im-a-racker/Rackspace_RookieO.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rackspace RookieO&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/im-a-racker/Rackspace_FuelStation.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rackspace Fanatical Jacket&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/im-a-racker/Rackspace_Slide.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rackspace GroundTown&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-goals&#34;&gt;My Goals&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a new big challenge, because means:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation in other country, specifically in San Antonio, TX, USA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave my family in Mexico City, that means that I see my parents only for Skype or FaceTime :).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know other culture, the &amp;ldquo;American&amp;rdquo; culture, with the Breakfast Tacos or Tex-Mex food (I really hate the Tex-Mex food yiack!) or the Lunch at noon, the people do not always says &amp;ldquo;Good morning&amp;rdquo; and some details that I don&amp;rsquo;t understand but here is common.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve my skills in other language (English) event though I&amp;rsquo;m in the Rackspace LATAM team all the communications like emails or meetings are in English, so, it is very important for my job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And the most important challenge for me is still learn about Linux, get my Red Hat Certifications, do my best at job and take advantage of this great opportunity. All of that to try to be a DevOps Engineer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/im-a-racker/Rackspace_MyDesk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Rackspace MyDesk&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be working on, providing Fanatical Support for our customers, resolving LATAM customer issues with Linux and working with remote teams from all around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summarizing, I&amp;rsquo;m a happy Racker 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
